// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which type of JavaScript language is-",
    answer: "Object-Based",
    options: [
      "Object-Oriented",
      "Object-Based",
      "Assembly-language",
      "High-level"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
    answer: "Immediate if",
    options: [
      "Alternative to if-else",
      "Switch statement",
      "If-then-else statement",
      "Immediate if"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
    answer: "Ignores the statements",
    options: [
      "Shows a warning",
      "Prompts to complete the statement",
      "Throws an error",
      "Ignores the statements"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: 'The "function" and " var" are known as:',
    answer: "Declaration statements",
    options: [
      "Keywords",
      "Data types",
      "Declaration statements",
      "Prototypes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression:",
    answer: "Function literal",
    options: [
      "Function prototype",
      "Function literal",
      "Function calling",
      "Function declaration"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
    answer: "Mutable variable",
    options: [
      "Mutable variable",
      "Dynamic variable",
      "Volatile variable",
      "Immutable variable"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?",
    answer: "Both 0x and 0X",
    options: [
      "00",
      "0x",
      "0X",
      "Both 0x and 0X"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
    answer: "Division by zero",
    options: [
      "Syntax error",
      "Missing of semicolons",
      "Division by zero",
      "Missing of Bracket"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
    answer: "valueOf()",
    options: [
      "toString()",
      "valueOf()",
      "toLocaleString()",
      "toPrecision()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:",
    answer: "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
    options: [
      "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
      "Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
      "Both are equal in the value and data type.",
      "Both are not same at all."
    ]
  },
];